poppin.com 2017-06-25

# Privacy Policy

Nice to meet you. We’re poppin. For those who care about these kinds of things, our full corporate name is poppin inc., and we are a Delaware corporation. 

Thank you for visiting us. We understand that you are mindful of how information about you is used and shared. We’ve put together this Privacy Policy (“Policy”) to describe how we collect, use, store, process, and share your information in relation to the Site. By the way, when we use the word “Site,” it’s really shorthand for both the poppin.com web site and any other of our applications (like mobile device applications, Facebook pages, etc.) that we may use to put all of our great products at your fingertips and that provide your information to us. 

When you visit or use the Site or place an order, you expressly consent to the collection, use, storage, processing, and disclosure of your information, including personally identifiable information, as described in this Policy. This Policy is part of and incorporated into the Terms of Use governing your use of the Site, so please be sure to review the Terms of Use prior to using the Site. **If there is something in this Policy that you don’t agree with, you should not use the Site or place an order.** In addition, you can only use the Site if you are over 18 years old. If you are under 18, you may use the Site only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. 

While we really like the way things are working right now, it is inevitable that we will change some things over time, as we learn more about you and how we can best serve you. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we modify it, we will post the new version right here, so it is important that you check back on a regular basis to see whether we’ve made any changes, as you will be agreeing to the new Privacy Policy by using the Site after the new version has been posted. For ease of reference, you can view the Last Updated date of this Policy at the top of the page. 

* * *

##### What information does Poppin collect?

We are fanatically driven to make your experience with us easier and better for you. So, wherever we can, we collect and store information that may make it easier for us to improve the shopping experience, display the product or content in which you are likely to be most interested, and make it easier for you to reorder without having to enter information you have already provided. 

* * *

#####  Information You Provide 

We collect personally identifiable information that you voluntarily provide to us when you use the Site, create an account, place an order, or communicate with us. Personally identifiable information is information that can identify you, for example, your name or email address. For example, we may collect your name, email address, postal address, phone number and credit card, information about the products you purchase or tell us you are interested in, your third-party account credentials (for example your log-in credentials for Facebook), and friends’ contact information (such as email addresses). We may also collect information you provide to us pursuant to promotional programs, such as contests. 

If you access the Site through Facebook Connect or other services like it, you understand that some content and information in your third party account may be transmitted to poppin, and that third party account information transmitted to us is covered by this Policy. 

* * *

#####  Content You Provide 

From time to time you may send us mail or email that gush about our products or services, videos that show how far your packing list can travel in the shape of an airplane, or other content. We will collect and store this information and reserve the right to use it for promotional purposes. 

* * *

#####  Information Collected by cookies 

When you visit the Site, we may send one or more “cookies” to your computer. A “cookie” is a small line of text that is stored with your Web browser, which allows us to recognize you when you return to the Site. Your browser has options to accept, reject or provide you with notice when a cookie is sent. Using cookies helps us serve you better. It allows us to do things like save items in your shopping cart, save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site, and deliver product recommendations and other content that are customized to fit your interest. If you would prefer that we not use cookies on your computer, feel free to set your browser to reject them; however certain features of the Site may not be available if your browser does not accept cookies. 

We may use third-party companies to help tailor Site content to users or to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and web beacons to measure advertising effectiveness (such as which web pages are visited or what products are purchased and in what amount). 

Google Analytics uses cookies and pixels in order to collect demographic and interest-level information and usage information from users that visit the Site, including but not limited to information about the pages where users enter and exit the Site and what pages users view on the Site, time spent, browser, operating system, and IP address. Cookies and pixels allow Google to recognize a user when a user visits the Site and when the user visits other websites. Google uses the information it collects from the Site and other websites to share with us and other website operators information about users including, but not limited to, age range, gender, geographic regions, general interests, and details about devices used to visit websites and purchase items. We do not link information we receive from Google with any of your personally identifiable information. For more information regarding Google’s use of cookies, pixels, and collection and use of information, please review [Google’s Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). If you would like to opt out of Google Analytics tracking, please visit the following link: [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

* * *

#####  Information Recorded by our Servers 

Our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit the Site, such as the pages you visit on our site, your Internet IP address, your browser type, the place on the Internet that you came from immediately before going to the Site, the place on the Internet that you go to immediately after leaving the Site, the amount of time you spent on particular pages and the date and time of your visit. 

* * *

#####  Information Collected by “Clear GIFs” 

We use “clear GIFs” (a.k.a. Web Beacons) to track online usage patterns anonymously. In addition, we also use clear GIFs in HTML-based emails we may send to you in order to track which emails are opened. 

* * *

#####  Product Reviews 

You may choose to submit a product review. If you post a review, we may ask for personally identifiable information such as an email address. Any personally identifiable information that you submit as part of the review can be read or used by other visitors to the Site. We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information that you choose to submit as part of your review. We believe you can post a helpful review without disclosing personal information. 

* * *

#####  Independent Reviews by Third Parties 

You may be asked to rate your experiences with us after you place an order with us. This choice is optional and it will not affect your order or service from us, whether or not you choose to provide feedback. Your feedback will be collected by an independent company and the information that you share is governed by their privacy policy. 

* * *

#####  Information from Other Sources 

We may receive information from other sources to help us serve you better. Examples include, but are not limited to, delivery and address information from our carriers which we use to correct our records. 

* * *

#####  How Does poppin Use Your Information? 

We use personally identifiable information you provide to process and fulfill your order, including to send you emails to confirm your order status and shipment. We also may use personally identifiable information we learn about you to customize our Site for you and to deliver product offers and other information that we think you would be interested in. Payment information will be used only to process payment transactions. 

We may also use personally identifiable information to resolve disputes; to detect and protect against errors, fraud, and criminal activity; to assist law enforcement; to enforce this Policy and the Terms of Use; or for any other purpose described in this Policy or that we describe to you at the time of collection. 

We may use non-personally identifiable information for any lawful purpose, including, but not limited to analyzing trends, administering the Site, tracking users’ movements on the Site, and for management and improvement of the Site. 

* * *

#####  Will poppin Share Information with Others? 

We may share information with any affiliated entity or organization and to agents and service providers. These third parties include various business services providers or providers that supply support for the Site or otherwise are working directly with us. Examples include for fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending emails, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, and processing credit card payments. 

We may share information when we believe its release is appropriate and necessary to comply with the law; to government regulators or law enforcement authorities in connection with any judicial proceeding, court order, subpoena or legal process served on us or the Site; to enforce or apply this Policy and the Terms of Use; or to protect the rights, property or safety of poppin, our employees and users. We may exchange information with other companies or organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

* * *

#####  How Does poppin Keep My Information Secure? 

We have implemented a number of security measures to protect your personally identifiable information and we have extra layers of security around your payment information. We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. In addition, your account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. It is important that you keep your password to yourself and log off once you have finished using a shared computer so that others can’t access your account. 

While we take measures to safeguard your personal information, we cannot ensure that all of your information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Policy. For example, a third party may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or other users of the Site may abuse or misuse your personal information. No transmission of data over the internet can be 100% secure. 

If poppin learns of a security system’s breach, we may attempt to notify you so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By providing personally identifiable information to us or using this Site, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy and administrative issues. 

* * *

#####  Special Notices 

**This Site Is Not for or Directed Towards Children**

Our primary audience is adults. While the Site is not for anyone under the age of 18, we certainly do not intend to and will not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13; children under the age of 18, and therefore children under the age of 13, are prohibited from using our Site without parent/guardian supervision. If we learn that we have collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will remove that information immediately and delete it from our servers (subject to applicable law and this Policy). If you believe information from a child under the age of 13 has been posted to our Site, please contact us at: [privacy@poppin.com](mailto:privacy@poppin.com). 

**California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of the Site who are California residents to obtain from us once a year, free of charge, a list of third parties to whom we have disclosed personal information (if any) for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and you wish to make such a request, please send an e-mail with “California Privacy Rights” in the subject line to [privacy@poppin.com](mailto:privacy@poppin.com) or write us at: 

Poppin Privacy Rights

1115 Broadway

3rd Floor

New York, New York 10010

**California Minors**

If you are a California resident who is under age 18 and you are unable to remove publicly-available content that you have submitted to us, you may request removal by contacting us at: [privacy@poppin.com](mailto:privacy@poppin.com). When requesting removal, you must be specific about the information you want removed and provide us with specific information, such as the URL for each page where the information is located, so that we can find it. We are not required to remove any content or information that: (1) federal or state law requires us or a third party to maintain; (2) was not posted by you; (3) is anonymized so that you cannot be identified; (4) you don’t follow our instructions for removing or requesting removal; or (5) you received compensation or other consideration for providing the Content or information. Removal of your content or information from the Site does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of that content or information from our systems or the systems of our service providers. We are not required to delete the content or information posted by you; our obligations under California law are satisfied so long as we anonymize the content or information or render it invisible to other users and the public. 

* * *

#####  Mergers, Acquisitions & Insolvency 

We expect to be around for the long haul. With that said, if poppin should ever file for bankruptcy or engage in a business transition such as a merger with another company, or if poppin decides to buy, sell or reorganize some part or all of its business, poppin may disclose your personal information, including to prospective or actual purchasers in connection with one of these transactions. 

* * *

#####  Note to International Users 

The Site and our products are not currently being offered outside the United States. Any information provided to us by you will be transferred to the United States and by using our Site or ordering products you consent to the transfer and use of your information, including personally identifiable information, in accordance with this Policy.
